

CONTACT

- 09706340680
- Virac Catanduanes
- https://mico322.github.io/ micotubice/

EDUCATION

2020 - 2024 CATANDUANES STATE UNIVERSITY

 Bachelor Of Science In Information System

SKILLS

- Computer Vision: Advanced Concepts and Troubleshooting skills.
- Data Management: Google
 Workspace, Chatgpt, Trello,
 Notion, Zoom and Microsoft
 Office Suite
- Design Tools: Adobe
 Photoshop, Canva Pro,
 Illustrator, Blender, Figma
- Front End Development:
 Html5, CSS3, Bootstrap,
 Git/GitHub, VS Code &
 Javascript (PHP,MySql)

MICO TUBICE

PROFILE

With a keen eye for detail and precision in data entry and management, I bring over years of experience in Adobe Photoshop to seamlessly blend creativity with meticulous organization. My ability to tackle challenges with efficiency and innovation ensures exceptional performance in both graphic design and data entry tasks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance - Onlinejob.ph

April 2022- August 2024

Virtual Personal Assistant

- Set up an automated blog on WordPress using the WP Automatic plugin, integrating APIs.
- Managed advertising campaign accounts on MGID and ADKP, bulk management of ad lists and performance analysis.
- Created custom thumbnails and engaging ads to enhance ad strategies and improve campaign effectiveness.
- Integrated ChatGPT AI API for automated data entry in blogging, streamlining content creation.
- Edited and troubleshot websites, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript bugs, which enhanced site functionality and user experience.
- Used Figma to create interactive web mockups, enabling client to visualize design concepts

Freelance - Onlinejob.ph

April 2024- May 2024

Product Label Designer

- Designed candy product labels Canva Pro and Adobe Photoshop.
- Provided mock-ups, made revisions based on feedback, and finalized designs.

Internship at DAR

Feb 2024 - May 2024

Product Design Intern

- Designed product labels for SARCO, RAGMO DAR's products
- Collaborated with clients to understand their needs, leading to redesigns of product labeling.
- Handled the design and production of banners, T-shirts, and employee IDs for DAR

CERTIFICATES

- Programming Java NC III | Joysis Tech Voc Inc | 2021 2022
- Computer Systems Servicing NC II | 2019 2019

REFERENCES

Ruben Tapit
SIB/SMEDSS
Department of Agrarian Reform OJT Supervisor
09209600137

